const tasksInput = [
  {
    title: 'A message to a new friend',
    text: "Hi Lucia! How are you? It was so nice to meet you last week in Sydney at the sales meeting. How was the rest of your trip? Did you see any kangaroos? I hope you got home to Mexico City OK. Anyway, I have the documents about the new Berlin offices. We're going to be open in three months. I moved here from London just last week. They are very nice offices, and the location is perfect. There are lots of restaurants, cafés and banks in the area. There's also public transport; we are next to an U-Bahn (that is the name for the metro here). Maybe you can come and see them one day? I would love to show you Berlin, especially in the winter. You said you have never seen snow – you will see lots here! Here's a photo of you and me at the restaurant in Sydney. That was a very fun night! Remember the singing Englishman? Crazy! Please send me any other photos you have of that night. Good memories. Please give me your email address and I will send you the documents. Bye for now Mikel",
    task1: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'Mikel and Lucia met here.',
        variant1: 'Sydney',
        variant2: 'Mexico City',
        variant3: 'London',
        variant4: 'Berlin',
        correct: 'Sydney',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: "Mikel's new offices are here.",
        variant1: 'Sydney',
        variant2: 'Mexico City',
        variant3: 'London',
        variant4: 'Berlin',
        correct: 'Berlin',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Mikel used to live here.',
        variant1: 'Sydney',
        variant2: 'Mexico City',
        variant3: 'London',
        variant4: 'Berlin',
        correct: 'London',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Lucia lives here.',
        variant1: 'Sydney',
        variant2: 'Mexico City',
        variant3: 'London',
        variant4: 'Berlin',
        correct: 'Mexico City',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'Mikel and Lucia were friends from school.',
        variant1: 'true',
        variant2: 'false',
        variant3: 'not mentioned',
        variant4: "I don't know",
        correct: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: 'They work for a company that sells things.',
        variant1: 'true',
        variant2: 'false',
        variant3: 'not mentioned',
        variant4: "I don't know",
        correct: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: 'The new offices are in a very good location.',
        variant1: 'true',
        variant2: 'false',
        variant3: 'not mentioned',
        variant4: "I don't know",
        correct: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: 'There is a metro next to the offices.',
        variant1: 'true',
        variant2: 'false',
        variant3: 'not mentioned',
        variant4: "I don't know",
        correct: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: 'Mikel has never seen snow before.',
        variant1: 'true',
        variant2: 'false',
        variant3: 'not mentioned',
        variant4: "I don't know",
        correct: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: 'Mikel and Lucia had dinner together.',
        variant1: 'true',
        variant2: 'false',
        variant3: 'not mentioned',
        variant4: "I don't know",
        correct: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 11,
        question: "Mikel doesn't have Lucia's email address.",
        variant1: 'true',
        variant2: 'false',
        variant3: 'not mentioned',
        variant4: "I don't know",
        correct: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 12,
        question: 'Lucia wants to send Mikel some documents.',
        variant1: 'true',
        variant2: 'false',
        variant3: 'not mentioned',
        variant4: "I don't know",
        correct: 'false',
      },
    ],
  },
];

export default tasksInput;
